[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Welcome.
&gt;&gt;欢迎各位
Good afternoon everyone.
大家下午好
I'm Sirisha from SiriKit
我是 Sirisha  来自 SiriKit
Engineering.
工程技术团队
I'm joined by my colleague and
今天我要和我的同事兼好友
friend Tin to talk about all the
Tin 一起聊聊我们今年
cool new features we are
将给 SiriKit 增添
bringing this year in SiriKit.
哪些酷炫的新功能
SiriKit was introduced last
我们去年推出了 SiriKit
year, a brand new way for
它以一种全新方式
everyone to do things in their
让每个人都能使用自己的语音来
apps using their voice.
吩咐 App 做事情
The main goal of the release was
这项发布的主要目的
to make sure to give you the
是为了确保大家能够
ability so your services and
把自己的服务和内容
content can be integrated with
与我们的 SiriKit 相结合
our SiriKit so users can now
这样一来 用户就能用 Siri
talk to their apps using Siri.
跟自己的 App 对话了
To make this happen, we've
为了实现这个目标 我们
opened up numerous domains like
已经开放了许多应用域
Workouts, Messages, Ride
比如训练、发消息、乘车预订等等
Booking, just to name a few.
以上列举的只是其中一部分
Every domain had one or more
每个应用域都包含一个或多个
intents.
Intent
And intents had a specific task
而这些 Intent 分别对应某个具体任务
like the Messaging domain.
例如  通过发送信息的应用域
Users were able to send a
用户可以发送
message or search a message.
或搜索一则信息
Ride Booking, everybody were
使用乘车预订，每个人
able to book ride in their
都能在自己喜欢的 App 里
preferred apps.
预订出行
Or paying bills in Payments
或者是通过付款应用
domain.
付款结账
Because of these intents, we
因为有了这些 Intent  我们
gave you the ability to pick and
使得大家能够挑选
choose the intents that you want
自己想要订阅 同时也
to register that best suited
最适合你的各项 App 功能
your app capabilities.
的Intent
In our release Watch 3.2 we
我们在发布 Watch 3.2 的时候
started supporting SiriKit on
就已经开始在 WatchOS 平台上
watchOS platform.
支持 SiriKit 运行
By writing a Watch extension you
通过编写 Watch Extension
were able to take all the
你可以在 Watch 上
advantages of SiriKit Intent
充分利用 SiriKit Intent
framework on the Watch.
框架的所有优点
As our ongoing effort to make
我们正在不断努力
your experience seamless and
给大家带来便捷流畅的体验
easy, we've added our support to
所以我们现在增加了
simulator.
对模拟器的支持
Starting iOS 10.3 and watchOS
启动 iOS10.3 和 watchOS3.2
3.2, you were able to debug and
你就能够在编写 SiriKit Extension 时
test while writing SiriKit
进行调试和
extension.
检测
This is a big year for us.
今年对我们来说意义非凡
Great reception and amazing
用户的广泛认同和绝妙反馈
feedback made this happen.
让这一切成为现实
Let's take a sneak peek about
我们不妨大致看一看
all the cool things we are
今年我们将给大家带来
bringing this year.
哪些酷炫的东西
A lot of new domains and many
我们开发了许多新的应用域
more intents.
和更丰富的 Intent
Brand new APIs to give you move
全新的 API（应用程序编程接口）让你拥有更多权限
control to customize the feel
在 Siri 里
and look at your apps view in
实现体验定制化
Siri.
并且察看自己的 App 视图
And lots of enhancements to our
我们还大力改进了
systems and APIs for a much
各个系统和 API 以便有效地
improved user experience.
提升用户体验
So, let's talk through the
那么 我们不妨先从
domains first.
应用域谈起
We've added new intents to our
我们已经把一些新的 Intent 添加到
Payments domain.
付款应用域
We've add our support to Lists
我们还增强了对列表和
and Notes functionality.
备忘录使用功能的支持
If your app uses visual codes,
如果你的 App 使用可视化代码
you can start integrating with
那么你可以着手考虑整合
SiriKit starting this fall.
今年秋天开始投入使用的 Sirikit 功能了
Payments was introduced in iOS
付款应用域是从 iOS10 就开始
10.
采用了
When we introduced, we added our
我们当初在做这款发布时 添加了
support to sending money and
支持付款和
requesting money.
收款的功能
In our 10.3 release we've added
我们在发布 10.3 版本时  又添加了
the support for bills.
查看账单的功能
Users were able to search for
用户能够查询账单
bills and pay bills.
并进行支付
We are extending our support
今年我们将进一步扩大支持内容
further this year by adding our
我们这次增添了对账户管理
support for accounts.
的支持
Users will now be able to
用户目前将能够
transfer money from one account
把钱从一个账户转移到
to another, or search for
另一个账户  或是查询
account information.
账户信息
Let's take a look at these.
我们现在来看看这些内容
First I'm going to talk about
首先我想谈谈
the transfer intent.
转账的 Intent
If you look at the screen, Siri
请看大屏幕  Siri 的
is very capable and powerful to
功能确实非常强大
understand such long requests.
它可以理解这么长的请求
For right now I'm just going to
现在我就给大家
walk through line by line.
逐行演示这些内容
Transfer $10 tomorrow.
明天转账 10 美元
$10 will be mapped as amount.
就有 10 美元被映射为转账金额
And tomorrow is converted to the
而明天 就被对应转换为
exact date.
具体执行日期
Easy. The transaction properties
搞定 这些交易特征
are simple and map rightly.
很简单 而且映射准确
What about accounts?
那么账户查询是什么情况呢？
Accounts can be referred in many
账户的命名方式
ways.
多种多样
I sometimes like to use it just
有时候我会用机构名称
by organization name.
来命名账户
Or, like an account type like
或者 就像我在这里使用的
I've used here: checking,
账户类型：活期账户
savings, credit.
存款和信用卡
Siri understands all times of
Siri 能弄清楚所有账户的
accounts and makes sure that it
时间段，并且能确保
infers rightly and then gives it
查询准确  然后把结果传到
to your app.
你的 App
Well and good.
干得漂亮
What is this Rainbow Savings?
这个 Rainbow Savings 又是什么？
This is the name I have used
这是我在自己的一个 App 里
when registering my account in
注册账户时使用过
one of my apps.
的名字
And I want to make sure that
现在我想确认一下
Siri understands my account
Siri 还能准确识别
nicknames, too.
我的账户别称
And how is this possible?
这是怎样实现的呢？
When you registered
如果你使用我们的
user-specific data using our IN
IN Vocabulary API 来注册
Vocabulary API, we will be able
用户详细资料 我们就能
to understand user's specific
了解到用户的具体
information.
信息
You can look for more
你可以在这个链接中
information of IN Vocabulary API
获取有关 IN Vocabulary API
in this link.
的更多信息
So, let's talk about Search.
好 我们再来谈谈查询环节
Our second intent is a Search
我们第二个 Intent 是查询
for Accounts intent, which will
账户的 Intent 它可以
be able to list all the account
如果用户恰好要求列出所有的
types if the user just asks to
账户  它就能列出所有的
list all the accounts.
账户类型
Just enough information to
信息量恰好足够
distinguish between the
用来区分
accounts, along with the
每个账户  外加它们的
balance.
余额
And if the user wants to know
如果用户想了解
more about each account, they
每个账户的更多详情
can just click on any of the
只需点开其中任意一项
item to get a detailed view.
来详细了解
Search for Accounts intent, not
账户查询 Intent 不仅
just shows all the accounts, but
显示所有账户 而且
also can be used to query for
还可以用来查看
specific account information.
具体的账户信息
Like here.
就像这样
What is the balance on my
我的 Rainbow Checking 账户里
Rainbow Checking account?
余额还有多少？
I'm asking specifically my
我现在具体询问的是我
balance on a specific account.
某个账户里的余额
And Siri perfectly understands
Siri 完全理解这一点
it and then gives the user the
所以它马上给用户提供了
required information.
所需要的信息
We don't only support the normal
我们不仅支持查询常规余额
balance, but also we've added a
我们还另外添加了
couple of balance types.
其他几种余额类型
Like if your app supports
比如说 如果你的 App 支持
airline mileages or reward
飞行里程累积 或者是
points.
奖励值
Siri can understand them as
Siri 同样也能识别
well.
它们
How many miles do I have on my
我的飞行里程已经积累多少到我的
Sparkle card?
Sparkle 卡里了呢？
Siri understands it and then
Siri 理解了 于是就把
passes it to your app.
里程数发送到你的 App
And thus giving the user the
就这样 给用户提供了
required information.
所需要的信息
So, INTransferMoneyIntent can be
所以，INTransferMoneyIntent 可以
used to transfer money from one
用来把钱从一个账户
account to another.
转到另一账户
INSearchForAccountsIntent can be
INSearchForAccountsIntent 可以
used to check balances, to list
用来查看余额  可以列出
all the accounts or to check any
所有账户  或者查看任何
specific account information.
账户的具体信息
That's all we have for Payments
这就是我们今年关于付款的
this year.
全部内容
With our analysis, we found out
根据分析 我们发现
that managing lists and notes is
管理列表和备忘录是
one of the very popular use
非常受 Siri 用户欢迎的
cases in Siri users.
实例之一
And so, this year we're
所以 今年我们准备
extending our support to support
加大力度  来支持
lists and notes.
列表和备忘录功能
We've added all the APIs to make
我们已经添加了所有的 API 用来
sure that users can create,
确保用户能够创建
edit, manage, their lists,
编辑和管理他们的列表
notes, and reminders.
备忘录和提醒
Not just that, but also users
不仅如此  用户还能在他们的
will be able to search in their
列表和备忘录中
lists and notes.
进行搜索
Let's take a look at them.
我们来看一下
This is an example to create a
这是一个创建列表的
list.
示例
I can ask Siri to create a list
我可以让 Siri 创建一个列表
by giving a title and also the
首先要给它提供一个标题
contents.
和内容
And Siri is powerful enough to
Siri 的强大功能足以
distinguish between them,
把它们加以区分
understand them, and pass on the
并且理解清楚  再传递出
right information, filling in
正确的信息  它填写好
the intent, giving it to you to
Intent 再提供给你
create the view.
用来创建视图
This is one of my favorite
这是我最喜欢的
intents: the joys of marking
Intent 之一：标记任务已完成
tasks done.
是一种乐趣
SetTaskAttributeIntent can be
SetTaskAttributeIntent 可以
used for this.
这样使用
This has a task type, which is
它有一个任务类型  包括
completed, not completed.
完成和未完成
And that carries the information
它在 Siri 和
between Siri and the app to make
和 App 之间传递信息 从而
sure that we do the action
确保我们的行动
correctly.
正确无误
We've added brand new intent to
我们添加了全新的 Intent（动机）来
support reminders.
支持提醒功能
We can create reminders in many
我们可以用许多方式来创建
ways.
提醒事项
Siri supports two types of
Siri 支持两种类型的
reminders: spatial and temporal.
提醒事项：空间类型和时间类型
Let's talk about spatial first.
我们先来说说空间类型
An example here: Remind me to
这里有个例子：在 UnicornNote 里
leave work at 5 p.m. in
提醒我在
UnicornNote.
下午 5 点收工
I'm asking Siri to remind me to
我现在再让 Siri 提醒我
print slide when I get to work.
一到办公室就打印幻灯片
I'm making -- I want Siri to
我正在--我要
make sure that it understands
确保 Siri 能明白
the geolocation of the word and
这个词的地理定位
then pass on the information to
然后再把信息传递给你
you so you can create the right
这样你就能给这个地理定位
reminder for the geolocation.
创建一个正确的提醒事项
The next example: Remind me to
下一个例子 提醒我
leave work at 5 p.m. This is to
下午 5 点收工  这样是
make sure that the date trigger
为了确保日期触发器
is created.
能够创建成功
If you look at both the
通过这两个例子
examples, Siri is powerful
你会发现 Siri 很强大
enough to understand when I said
它完全能理解我所说的
"leave work at 5 p.m."
“下午5点收工”
to create a date reminder, but
然后就创建一份日期提醒事项
not a location reminder for
而不是创建一份
leaving work.
地点事项的提醒下班这件事
And in the before example, Siri
在前面那个例子里  Siri
created a location trigger when
创建了一个地点触发器
I said "arrive at work."
因为我说了“一到办公室”
Siri is very powerful in parsing
Siri 十分擅长对你使用的这些语句
these use cases and
进行语法分析
understanding them to create the
Siri 能够理解它们  并用来创建
right intent and pass it over to
正确的 Intent 然后再传送
you.
给你
So, CreateTaskIntent can be used
因此  CreateTaskIntent 可以用来
to create tasks, lists.
创建任务和列表
AddTasksIntent for the reminders
AddTasksIntent 可以创建提醒事项
and adding tasks to the existing
并在已有的提醒事项中添加
ones.
新任务
SetTaskAttributeIntent to set a
SetTaskAttributeIntent 是用来创建
task or to mark it completed or
任务 或标明任务已完成
to update it to a reminder.
或是把它更新到提醒事项里
Let's talk about the notes.
我们现在来说说备忘录
Notes can be created in many
备忘录的创建可以有许多
ways.
方式
I can create by using the title,
我可以通过标题来创建
the content and even under a
也可以通过内容  甚至是在
folder.
文件夹里创建
And Siri supports all these
Siri 支持所有这些
options.
选项
So when I ask Siri to create a
所以当我让 Siri 创建一份
note with just given title, it
备忘录时 只给了特定标题
just creates a blank note.
它就只创建一个空白备忘录
I can also ask Siri to create a
我可以让 Siri 在特定的
note under a specific folder
文件夹下面 根据内容
along with its content.
创建一个备忘录
Siri parses the whole user
Siri 对用户的整体意图进行
intent and then maps the
语法分析  然后把
appropriate title, group name,
贴切的标题、群组名
and content into the intent and
和内容映射到 Intent
then pass it over to you to
然后再把它传送给你
create the right note.
以便创建合适的备忘录
And adding to an existing note.
至于在现有的备忘录里进行添加
This is possible with Siri, too.
Siri 也同样可以做到
Here, Siri understands the
看这里  Siri 将目标备忘录
target note as WWDC.
理解为 WWDC
And then the actual content.
然后就是实际内容
And then passes the information
接着再把信息传送给你
over to you to create the note.
让你创建备忘录
Let's take a look at the
我们再来看看
intents.
各种 Intent
CreateNoteIntent to create brand
CreateNoteIntent 是用来创建
new notes.
全新的备忘录
AppendToNoteIntent to add to an
AppendToNoteIntent 是往已经存在的
existing one.
备忘录里添加内容
The next big intent in the Lists
在列表和备忘录里，另一个重要的
and Notes is Search.
Intent 就是 Search
When you get asked to just show
如果有人让你展示一下
all the information, Siri
所有的信息  Siri
understands and then passes the
会理解指令  然后将这个
intent to your app.
Intent 发送到你的 App
And Siri lists all the notes,
Siri 还把所有经过 App 传送给我们的
lists, reminder, passed on by
备忘录 列表和提醒事项
the app to us.
列出清单
We can display as is if you want
我们的显示效果 就像你要求我们
us to.
做出来的一样
Or, you also have the option of
或者  你还可以选择说
mentioning it to be sorted by
把它按照日期分类
date, where Siri will go ahead
这样 Siri 就会照办
and sort all the items by date.
把所有项目按日期分类
And then show it to the user.
然后再展示给用户
Not just showing all the items,
用户不仅可以展示所有项目
but user can also query using a
还可以只用某个具体类型
specific type, like show just
进行查询  比如只展示
the notes or just the lists.
备忘录 或者只展示列表
Or show the notes I created
或者是展示我昨天创建的
yesterday.
备忘录
Or even show my completed tasks.
甚至只展示我已经完成的任务
There are many types we support
我们使用这种 Intent
under this intent.
可以支持很多类型
And the intent itself is called
这个 Intent 本身叫做
SearchForNotebookItemIntent.
SearchForNotebookItemIntent
And it supports all these types.
它支持所有这些类型
So user can ask if using any one
因此用户可以看一看 如果使用
of these and Siri will
其中的一种  Siri 会不会
understand perfectly and thus
完全理解，然后
completing the action.
完成任务
And that's all the Notes and
以上就是我们所有关于
Lists new APIs we have.
备忘录和列表的新 API
Visual codes like QR codes, Bar
现在的各种可视码  比如二维码
Codes, are becoming very popular
条形码  近来已经
these days.
非常流行
They're being used in numerous
目前它们在 App 里有各种
ways in the apps.
使用方法
Like they're used to just open a
比如说  它们可以用来打开网页
web page instead of typing a
而不再需要输入一堆
tedious URL, especially they're
无聊的网址  特别是当这些网址使用的
in foreign languages.
还是外语的时候
Just showing a QR code opens a
展示一下二维码  就可以打开
web page.
一个网页
Or using them to send payment or
或者用它们付款
request payment just by showing
或者发起收款 只要出示
a code.
代码就可以了
Paying at a gas station or
在加油站付费或者
paying to friends.
给朋友转账都可以
Apps are using bar codes to
现在各种 App 都使用条形码
perform specific tasks.
来执行具体任务
And not just bar codes or QR
我们不仅考虑到条形码或
codes.
二维码
We are also having codes as
我们在用于联络交往的 App 里还使用
contacts in networking apps to
作为联系方式的代码
connect to each other instead of
把它们和联系方式相关联  这样就不用
going finding a person and then
翻看查找某个人  然后
connecting.
再联系了
By just showing a contact code,
只要出示联系码
we are able to connect easily.
我们能够轻松获得联系
And starting iOS 11 Siri will be
从 iOS11 开始  Siri 就可以
supporting visual codes.
支持各种可视码了
Users will now be able to say
用户现在只要说一声
"Show my UnicornChat code,"
“出示我的 UnicornChat 码”就可以
which means Siri understands
也就是说  Siri 能理解
that this is a visual code
这是一种可视码 Intent
intent, and then pass on the
它随后就把信息
information to your app.
发送给你的 App
Whereas if the code could -- we
只要是用代码能办到的  因为我们
support different types of
支持不同类型的
codes, depending upon what app
代码  这要看 App 能为我们
gives us, we share it back to
提供什么了  我们都会给客户
the user.
回馈分享
And the intent that can be used
可以用来实现这个功能的
to this functionality is
Intent 就是
INGetVisualCodeIntent.
INGetVisualCodeIntent
It has one property type,
它有一种属性类型
visualCodeType, which supports
即 visualCodeType  这个类型可以支持的是
-- it could be a contact or a
它可以是一个联系人
request payment or send payment.
或付款请求  或者是转账付款
By registering to this intent
通过注册这个 Intent
users will be able to ask Siri
用户就能够让 Siri
to show the visual codes of any
在自己喜欢的 App 里显示这些类型里
of these types in their favorite
的任何一种
apps.
可视码
Now I invite my colleague and
现在  有请我的同事
friend Tin over to show you this
兼好友 Tin 上台  让他给大家实际展示
in action.
这个操作过程
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you Sirisha.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 Sirisha
Hi everybody.
大家好
My name is Tim.
我的名字是 Tin
And I'm engineer on the Siri
我是 Siri 客户团队的
Client Team.
工程师
So last year at WWDC we
在去年的 WWDC  我们
introduced an app called
向大家介绍了一款 App
UnicornChat.
它名叫 UnicornChat
It was great.
它非常棒
Let our unicorn friends, like
现在就让我们的 Unicorn 好友 比如
Celestra here, send messages to
今天在场的 Celestra  用它发送信息给
Sparkle Sparkly.
Sparkle Sparkly
And it was great.
确实非常棒
This year we want to add the
今年我们想增加
brand new Visual Code Intent
全新的可视码 Intent
support to the app.
来支持这款 App
And it's super simple.
它极其简单
So the first thing we want to do
所以我们要做的第一件事是
is we want to make sure to
确保能够
modify our info.plist.
修改我们的 info.plist.
If your app hasn't yet adopted
如果你的 App 还没有安装
SiriKit, all you need to do is
SiriKit  那么你要做的就是
to go and create in it
在 App 里创建一个
IntentsExtensionTarget in your
IntentsExtensionTarget 到
project, and you'll have the
在你的项目里 然后就会生成
info.plist, which you can edit.
可编辑的 info.plist
Once you have it, go ahead and
只要有了 info.plist  你就能继续
add under the Intents Support
在 Intent 支持键下面
Key the new visuaCodeIntent.
添加新的 visualCodeIntent
The next thing that's important
下一个需要
to notice is your principal
重点注意的  是你的
class.
主要类
The principal class is where
主要类指的是
Siri will call into your app and
Siri 将调用你的 App
ask you to begin handling your
并让你动手处理你的
intent.
Intent
And that's where we're going to
我们就从这里开始
begin modifying our application.
修改我们的应用
I'm also going to modify the
我还会修改
intents extension scheme and
Intent Extension 方案
fill out this field Siri Intent
并填完这份 Siri Intent 的
Query.
现场查询
I can prepopulate it with text
我可以预先用文本填写
to show my UnicornChat code.
以便展示我的 UnicornChat 码
This way every single time I
这样一来 我每次
build and run, Siri will
创建和运行时  Siri 都会
prepopulate that text.
预先填写这份文本
I don't need to speak to it
我不用每一次都向它
every single time.
下达口令
This will make debugging and
这样就能加快调试和
development much faster.
开发的速度
Let's code now.
我们现在一起来编码
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Let's take a look at the demo.
我们来看一下演示内容
So here I am in my principal
大家看  我现在展示的主要类
class of my intents extension
属于我在 UnicornChat 里使用的
for UnicornChat.
Intent 扩展
And we're already hailing the
我们已经在调用
SendMessageIntent.
SendMessageIntent
So let's go ahead now and handle
那么我们现在继续处理
that VisualCodeIntent.
这个 VisualCodeIntent
It's pretty easy.
非常简单
If you're handling multiple
如果你正在你的应用里
intents within your application,
处理多个 Intent
it's a great idea to split them
那么  把它们分割成
up across multiple classes.
多个类别  是个好主意
This separates your logic and
这样可以区分你的逻辑
makes things easier to test and
可以更方便地进行测试和
debug.
调试
So let's go now into our
好  我们现在进入
VisualCodeIntentHandler class.
VisualCodeIntentHandler 类
As a reminder, you need to do
提醒一下 你需要做好
three things when you're
三件事
handling a SiriKit intent.
来处理一项 SiriKit 的 Intent
The first thing you want to do
首先要做的是
is to resolve your intent.
解析你的 Intent
Resolving gives you an
通过解析 你可以
opportunity to customize Siri's
有机会自定义 Siri 的
properties and how it handles
属性  以及它处理
the properties of the intent.
Intent 属性的方式
Second, is Confirm.
第二件事  是确认
Confirm gives you the place to
确认过后 你就有办法
tell Siri a ready signal, that
向 Siri 发出准备信号  就是说
you're ready to handle the
你已经准备要处理
intent, as well as do
这个 Intent 同时进行
validation.
验证
Finally, you'll just go ahead
最后 你可以继续操作
and handle your intent.
并处理你的 Intent
For this VisualCodeIntent, we'll
至于这个 VisualCodeIntent  我们将
return an image and tell Siri to
返回一张图片 并让 Siri
display it.
把它展示出来
So let's go ahead and get
那么我们就来
started.
试一下吧
I'll make my class conform to
我要让这个 Intent 的类符合
the INGetVisualCodeIntent
INGetVisualCodeIntent 的
handling protocol.
处理协议
And the compiler's telling me I
现在  编译器提示我
need to implement some required
需要执行某些
methods.
规定方法
Go ahead and do that.
继续  这样操作
So the only required method is
那么作为要求的唯一规定方法就是
the Handle method.
Handle 方法
But we strongly recommend you
但是我们强烈建议大家
implement both Resolve and
完整执行解析和
Confirm.
确认这两个步骤
This is going to give you the
这样可以让你
most control and customization
最大限度地控制和自定义
over your user's behavior within
你在 Siri 里的
Siri.
用户行为
I'm going to move this out of
我现在暂时
the way for now.
跳过这个环节
And we'll implement Resolve
让我们首先来执行解析
first.
这个步骤
Again, resolution is where you
再说一遍 解析是让你能够
customize your behavior for
自定义你的行为 让它对应
Siri's properties of the intent.
这个 Intent 在 Siri 里的属性
For the VisualCodeIntent,
关于 VisualCodeIntent
there's only one property, and
它只有一个属性
that's the VisualCodeType.
那就是 VisualCodeType
As Sirisha mentioned, it could
Sirisha 刚才提到过  它可以
be a contact code, a payment
是联系码  收款码
request code, payment send code.
或者是付款码
So let's implement our custom
现在来执行一下我们的
logic now.
自定义逻辑
Here, if the user asks for a
这时候  如果用户需要一个
contact code, we'll tell Siri
联系码  我们就会告诉 Siri
we're going to handle it
我们准备把它有效处理为一个
successfully as a contact code
联系码的
type.
类型
If the user doesn't specify
如果用户没有明确表示
which kind of code they want,
他们想要哪种类型的代码
like they say "Show my code"
比如  他们用 UnicornChat 说的只是
using UnicornChat, Siri will
“展示我的代码”  Siri 就会
populate the type as unknown.
把这种类型填充为“未知”
And here we can customize the
我们这时可以对这种行为进行
behavior and also tell Siri we
自定义  并且告诉 Siri
want to handle that as a contact
我们要把它处理为
code type.
联系码类型
We won't support Payment Send or
我们不准备在这个演示版 App 里支持
Payment Request in our demo app.
付款和收款
So we'll tell Siri it's
所以我们就要告诉 Siri
unsupported.
不支持这种操作
And when we do so, if the user
这样做以后 如果用户
asks for a payment code, Siri
请求付款码  Siri
will intelligently dial out to
就会非常机智地使用它
the user in all the languages
支持的所有语言
that Siri supports.
跟用户会话
We don't have to write a single
我们一行代码都不用
line.
写出来
So that's the power of SiriKit.
这就是 SiriKit 的强大之处
Now we're done resolving the
现在我们已经解析了
properties.
各种属性
Let's go ahead and confirm this.
接下来 就是进行确认
So confirmation, again, is where
再次声明 确认就是
we give Siri that ready signal.
我们给 Siri 发出准备完毕的信号
And it's a great place to do
使用这个环节可以很好地
validation.
进行验证
So we want to make sure that our
接下来  我们首先要确认
Unicorn user has a valid and
我们这位 Unicorn 用户已经拥有一个
active account before we show
有效而活跃的账号 然后我们再展示
that contact code.
这个联系码
If they do, we'll go ahead and
如果他们有这样的账号  我们就会继续
return Ready response code to
把“准备完毕”的反馈码回复
Siri.
给 Siri
But what happens if the user
但是用户如果没有一个有效帐号
doesn't have a valid account?
情况又会怎样？
Well, it'd be great to launch
好，只要启动我们的 App
our app and be able to perhaps
就行  这样或许就能
ask them to sign up or
让他们进行登录 或者是
reactivate their account.
重新激活自己的账号
And we can do that using a
我们可以通过
custom user activity.
自定义用户操作来实现这一点
So we'll create a custom user
所以我们要用一个自定义用户信息词典
activity with a custom user info
来创建一项自定义用户的操作行为
dictionary with our error
我们的失误 将会在其中
specified.
标注清楚
And we'll turn to Siri
我们现在换个题目来谈谈 Siri 的
failureRequiringAppLaunch and
failureRequiringAppLaunch  并且
pass the user activity.
把用户的操作传递出去
Now, if the user asks for a code
好 如果用户请求代码
and they haven't signed up or
但他们既没有注册  也
their account's inactive, Siri
没有激活账号 Siri
will show an error and give the
会显示错误  并给用户
user an opportunity to launch
一次机会  来启动
the app.
App
And if they launch the app, the
如果他们启动了这个 App
user activity is passed on to
用户操作就会被传输给
the app.
App
And then you can extract that
然后你就可以提取
information, ask them to sign
这个信息  并要求他们
up.
注册
Make sure they can connect with
以确保他们可以连接到
their Unicorn friends.
自己的 Unicorn 好友
So now we're done with Confirm.
这样我们就完成了确认环节
Let's go and handle this.
接下来 让我们来处理这一项
Handle's very straightforward.
Handle 非常简单明确
We're just going to return a
我们只要在响应时
success code to Siri in the
把完成代码返回给 Siri
response.
就可以了
And we'll set the visual code
我们将把这次响应中的
image property on that response
可视码映像的属性
to be our contact code image.
设定为我们的联系码映像
So this looks pretty good.
这看起来很不错
Let's build and run now.
现在我们先创建 再运行一下试试
It's prepopulated my request.
它已经预先填充了我的请求
And there we have it.
这样就完成了
Our brand new visual code.
一个全新的可视化代码
Looks great.
看起来很棒
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So let's switch back now to
那么我们现在切换回
slides and recap.
幻灯片 再简要复述一下
So when supporting intents, all
为了支持这些 Intent  你只要
you need to do is remember to
记住修改一下
modify your info.plist.
你的 info.plist 文件
Again, if you don't have an
但是  如果你没有
info.plist, just go ahead and
info.plist 文件  你只需要
create a new Intents Extension
在 App 里创建一个新的
Target in your app and you can
Intent Extension（意图扩展）目标设定为
edit it.
你的 App 之后就能对它进行编辑
Next, make sure to modify your
接下来 一定要修改
principal class, handle that
你的主要类  接着再处理
intent.
这个 Intent
Finally, Resolve, Confirm and
最后对你的 Intent 进行
Handle your intent.
解析  确认和处理
Super simple.
超级简单
All right.
好了
I'd like to switch gears a
现在 我稍微转换一下话题
little bit and talk about
我们来聊一聊
customizing your UI within Siri.
怎样在 Siri 里自定义你的 UI
As a reminder, there's two types
提醒一下 Siri 里有两种类型的
of extensions in Siri.
Extension
The first type is the Intents
第一种类型是 Intent Extension
Extension, which you just saw.
就是你们刚才看到的那个
It's where you do your Resolve,
它是你在解析
Confirm, Handle, handle your
确认和处理时使用 用来处理你的
business logic.
事务逻辑
This is required.
这是必需的
The second type is an Intent UI
第二种类型是 Intent UI
extension where you can use to
extension  你可以用它
configure your view.
配制你的视图
And this is what we're going to
我们接下来要讨论的
be talking about now.
就是这个
So, in iOS 10, we let you
那么  在 iOS10 里  你可以
customize parts of your view.
自定义一部分视图
Here's a RequestWriteIntent.
这是一个 RequestWriteIntent
And we allowed you to customize
你可以自定义
certain parts of the view like
视图的部分内容 比如说
replacing the map with your own
把这个地图换成你的
custom view here.
自定义视图
We really like unicorns here.
我们真的喜欢 Unicorn 的这些特点
So, this was great.
这个很棒
It lets you show additional
它能够让你添加显示更多的
information, your own style.
信息  根据你的个人风格
But we noticed sometimes there
但我们还注意到  有时也存在
are issues.
一些情况
There's duplicate information,
比如信息重复问题
like this pickup location, drop
就像这里的乘车地点  和下车
off location are duplicated.
地点  它们就重复了
Same with the fare.
车费也是同样的情况
This is because you didn't have
这是因为你先前没有
full control over all the visual
完全掌握 Siri 里所有的
elements within Siri.
视图元素
Well, this year in iOS 11 we're
不过在今年的iOS 11里  我们
going to give you that full
将会让你实现
control.
完全掌控
And in order to do that, I'm
为了做到这一点  我准备
going to explain it to you a
向大家稍微解释一下
little bit how Siri draws its
Siri 是怎样绘制
views.
视图的
Siri represents its views as a
Siri 视图的呈现方式
stacked series of UI elements,
是以 UI 元素的栈结构系列来完成
each of which is backed by data
系列里的每一个元素都由
called a parameter.
命名为参数的数据来提供支持
So for example, the map is
举个例子  支持这份地图的
backed by a pickup location
是一个乘车地点参数
parameter, so on and so forth
其他的视图
for the rest of their views.
也与此类似
The ride option name, drop off
乘车方式选项名称  下车
location and so on.
地点等等
Here's another example.
再举一个例子
Here Sparkle Sparkly is coming
现在 Sparkle Sparkly 正准备
to pick us up in a majestic
开着一款很气派的 Unicorn 汽车
unicorn.
来接我们
And he's represented by -- this
那么代表他的  代表这个视图的
view is represented by two
就是这样的两个
parameters, a ride driver and a
参数  一个是搭载司机的参数
ride vehicle parameter.
一个是搭载车辆的参数
So some views can be represented
所以 有些视图可以通过
by multiple parameters or sets
多个参数或多组参数
of parameters.
来代表
In iOS 11 we expose this as a
我们在 iOS11 里 把它作为一个新的
new class called INParameter.
分类来公布  并称为 INParameter
And this is a class representing
这个分类代表了
that data.
这种数据
So here's the pickup location
那么 这里是乘车地点的
INParameter.
INParameter
It's constructed using a
它是通过一个
parameter class.
参数分类而构成
In this case the
这个例子里用的是
RequestRideIntent.
RequestRideIntent
And then a key path which is a
然后是作为属性的
property -- a location to a
关键路径  在这个分类里面导向
property on that class.
某个属性的位置
So the parameter represents a
所以参数代表着
sort of key to the value.
一种获取值的方式
And we want to be able to get
同时我们希望能够
the actual value, too.
获得真值
So there's a new method also on
因此在 INInteraction 这方面
the INInteraction called
还有一个新方法 叫做
parameterValue.
参数值
When you pass the parameter into
当你将参数传递到
the interaction, you'll get back
交互过程中  就将获得
the actual value.
真值
For the pickup location, it
至于乘车地点  它就会成为
would be a CL placemark object.
一个 CL 位置标记对象
Different parameters will have
不同的参数将拥有
different parameter value types.
不同的参数值类型
For example, the price range
比如  价格区间参数
parameter would have an
就会对应于
INPriceRange type.
INPriceRange 类型
So, with this concept of
因此 根据这样的参数
parameters, we can go from
概念 我们就可以让你
giving you control over a single
的掌控范围从单一视图
view to all of the views,
扩展到所有的视图
customizing them for parameters.
把它们自定义为不同参数
And we'll walk through that now.
我们现在就可以做到这一点了
This is the principal class of
这是 Intent UI Extension 的
the intents UI extension.
主要分类
It conforms to
它符合
INUIHostedViewControlling.
INUIHostedViewControlling 协议
This is the same as before.
这跟前面的情况相同
And our new method is called
我们的新方法叫作
configureViewFor parameters.
configureViewFor 参数
So you'll be asked to configure
这样的话  你就需要给一系列
your view for a set of
参数来配制
parameters.
你的自定义视图
You'll be given an interaction
你会获得一个交互
object.
对象
This will let you resolve those
让你来解析这些
parameter values.
参数值
You'll be given a context.
你还会获得一个语境
This will tell you whether
它会告诉你
you're being drawn within maps
你是在地图应用
or within Siri.
还是在 Siri 里进行绘制
And then finally, you'll be
这样到了最后 你会
given a completion block.
获得一个完成块
And you'll call this and it has
你可以调用它
three parameters.
它含有三个参数
The first is a Boolean.
首先是布尔数据类型
You'll return True or False
你在这时要
here.
返回 True 或 False
True meaning you wish to draw a
True 表示你想给
custom view for this set of
这组参数绘制
parameters.
自定义视图
False means you want to let Siri
False 表示你想让 Siri
draw its default view.
绘制默认视图
Second is the set of parameters
第二组参数就是
that you're handling if you
当你选择返回 True 时
choose to return True.
所要处理的参数
Finally, you return a size for
最后 你给 Siri 返回你的视图尺寸
your view for Siri to draw.
让它进行绘制
Let's walk through a concrete
下面 我将通过一个具体的例子
example and show you how we can
来给大家展示  我们是如何
customize a Request Ride
运用参数来自定义
Interaction using parameters.
乘车交互过程的
We'll make more unicorns.
我们要制造更多的 Unicorn
So, on top is Siri.
如图 最上方的是 Siri
Bottom is your Intents
最下方是你的那些 Intent
UIExtension.
UIExtension
You're first going to get called
首先 你要通过一组空参数
with an empty set of parameters.
来获得调用
This will give you a chance to
这样你就有机会
draw additional information,
获得额外信息
handle parameters up front, and
来处理我们先前所说的参数
for this case in our example,
那么  我们这个例子里的情况
will return False.
是要返回 False
Meaning we want to let Siri draw
这就意味着我们想让 Siri
the default view for this
为这个参数而绘制
parameter.
默认视图
And the default view for an
而一组空参数的
actually no view.
实际上为空白视图
This is how it looks like in
它用代码表现时  外观就是
code.
这样
Now, Siri needs to keep calling
现在 Siri 需要继续调用
configureView until it resolves
configureView 直到它解析完
all the parameters for the
所有应用于此次交互的
interaction.
参数
So the next view -- or the next
下一个视图 或者说 下一组
set of parameters is the pickup
参数  就是乘车
location.
地点
So it's going to ask you to
所以它需要你
configure your view for this
给这个环节
section.
配置你自己的视图
This time we're going to turn
这一次 我们要返回的是
True.
True
We're going to tell Siri we're
我们准备告诉 Siri 我们
going to handle that pickup
要处理那个乘车
location.
地点
And then the size for our custom
接下来就是我们自定义视图的
view.
尺寸
When we do this, Siri will
当我们这样操作时 Siri 会
replace its default view with
把默认视图替换为
our custom view.
我们的自定义视图
And it will remove all instances
而且 它会彻底移除自己原先
of the default view it would
准备绘制的默认视图的
have drawn.
系统进程
Finally, it will respect the
最后 它将遵照
size that we asked for.
我们要求设置的尺寸
So here's how it looks like in
这就是使用代码操作的
code.
情况
We'll go ahead and define our
接下来 我们将继续定义我们的
pickup location parameter.
乘车地点参数
We configure our view when we're
当我们根据要求  配置
asked to configure for the
乘车地点时
pickup location.
就会对视图进行配置
And tell Siri True, and we're
把 True 返回给 Siri  告诉它  我们
handling it.
正在处理
And finally we'll move our False
最后 我们将把 False 的
completion to an else block.
完成转移到某个 else block 代码块
So Siri, again, is going to keep
这样 Siri 将会继续
calling configureView until it
调用 configureView  直到它
resolves all the parameters.
把所有参数解析完毕
Then next is the ride option
接下来是搭乘选项的
name.
名称
And not only can you tell Siri
你不仅可以向 Siri 返回 False
False, to let it draw a default
让它绘制默认视图
view, or configure one parameter
或者每次设置一个参数
at a time, you can actually tell
其实 你还可以告诉
Siri you want to configure
Siri  你想要一次设置
multiple parameters at a time.
多个参数
Or all the rest of the
或者所有剩余的
parameters.
参数
So here we're going to tell Siri
那么现在 我们准备告诉 Siri
we're going to handle the ride
我们打算处理搭乘选项的
option name and then all the
名称  然后处理
rest of the parameters in the
视图里剩下的所有
view.
参数
And Siri will place all those
Siri 将把所有这些
parameters with our custom view.
参数都设置成我们的自定义视图
And Siri will no longer ask us
而且 Siri 不会再要求我们
to configure the view any
进一步配置视图
further because we've told it
因为我们已经告诉它
we're handling the parameters.
我们要处理这些参数
Here's how it looks like in
这是以代码形式显示的
code.
操作情况
We configure our parameters.
我们配置自己的参数
We've commented this part out.
这一部分在前面已经评论过了
Pick up location's just like
乘车地点的设置
before.
如前所述
Here we're handling the ride
现在 我们要处理搭乘选项的名称
option name and all the rest of
以及剩下的所有
the parameters.
参数
And then our completion, False.
然后我们实现完成  Flase
So we go from this view, which
我们从这个视图出发
has duplicate methods to be able
它可以使用重复方法来
to control all of the views and
控制所有视图以及
all the parameters for those
应用于这些视图的所有
views.
参数
And not only can we do this type
我们不仅可以完成这种类型的
of layout, we can do any type of
布局  我们还可以做出任何想要的
custom layout we want.
自定义布局
We can draw some custom views.
我们可以绘制一部分自定义视图
We can have Siri draw the rest.
可以让 Siri 绘制其余的视图
You can draw all custom views.
你可以绘制所有的自定义视图
Have a custom header.
创建一个自定义标题
So, it's super powerful.
可见 它超级强大
So let's take a look at this
那么 让我们来看看它在
live in Xcode.
Xcode 里的现场操作情况
Customize our Unicorn Ride app.
对我们的 Unicorn 乘车 App 进行自定义
We're going to use a pink theme.
我们打算选用粉色主题
Unicorns love pink.
独角兽(Unicorn)喜爱粉色
And we're going to handle two
我们准备处理两个
views.
视图
We're going to handle the fare
我们要处理车费和
and special pricing parameters
特价的参数
on the top view.
放在视图顶端
And then pickup location, drop
然后是乘车地点、下车地点
off location, ride option name
搭乘选项名称
on the bottom.
放在视图底部
And again, I'll use the Siri
我将再次使用 Siri 的
Intent Query feature to
Intent 查询功能来
prepopulate a request.
预先填写一项请求
So let's take a look at a demo
让我们再看一遍
again.
演示
So here I am in my principal
现在打开我在
class for my Intents UI
Intents UI extension 的
Extension.
主要分类
It conforms to the
它遵循的是
INUIHostedViewControlling
INUIHostedViewControlling
protocol.
协议
And let's go ahead and implement
我们继续来执行
that new configureView method.
新的 configureView 方法
The first time around, I'll
先开始第一遍 我会
return False to every single
在每个单独步骤都会返回
thing.
False
So Siri is going to draw its
那么 Siri 就会
default views for all the
为所有参数绘制
parameters.
默认视图
We can also put brake points
我们也可以在调试时
here during debugging to see
将断点放置在这里
which sets of parameters we're
看看哪几组参数
getting called for in which
是我们要调用的  还有它们是
order for the interaction as
按照什么顺序
well.
进行交互的
Let's build and run this.
我们来构建运行一下
All right.
好
We've got our default view here
我们要的默认视图有了
because we've told Siri False to
因为我们已经告诉 Siri
all the parameters.
对所有参数都设置 False
This isn't very Unicorny, so
这可不太符合 Unicorn 的风格 那么
let's get started and make it
我们就来动动手 让它变得
more pink.
更粉嫩一些
Let's take care of that fare and
我们来调整一下车费和
special pricing parameters.
特价的参数
So back in our controller.
所以 先回到控制器界面
We'll define parameters that
我们要界定
we're handling, fare and special
需要处理的参数 包括车费和
pricing.
特价参数
We'll handle our parameters and
我们将处理这些参数
then extract the real values for
然后从交互对象的
these parameters from the
第一个要求
interaction object on that first
也就是当 Siri 要求我们
call when Siri asks us to
配置一个空白的参数集时
configure for an empty set of
为这些参数提取出
parameters.
真值
Next, we'll take our parameter
下一步 我们将使用这些参数值
values, go ahead and use it to
继续用它来
configure our Unicorn Ride View.
配置我们的 Unicorn 乘车视图
And then we'll tell Siri we're
然后再告诉 Siri  我们要为
handling the custom view for
这些参数来处理
these parameters, and then the
自定义视图  并规定它的
size.
尺寸
Go ahead and move this to an
我们继续 把这个移动到某个
else block.
else-block 代码块
Let's build it around this.
让我们根据这个来构建视图
And it's looking a lot better.
现在看起来好多了
We got our pink view here
我们要的粉色视图有了
handling the fare and special
它可以处理车费和
pricing.
特价
And because we've returned False
由于我们把 False 返给了
to the rest of the parameters,
其余这些参数
Siri's drawing the default views
所以 Siri 正在绘制默认视图
for pickup location, drop off
包括乘车地点、下车地点
location, ride option name.
还有搭乘选项名称
So to fully customize our view,
所以 为了充分完成自定义视图
let's go ahead and take care of
我们就要继续处理
the rest of the parameters.
其余的参数
Here we're just defining the
现在我们只是在定义
rest of our parameters, just
剩下的一些参数
like before.
就像先前一样
Once again, we're configuring
我们将再一次配置
our view.
视图
When Siri asks for the pickup
当 Siri 询问乘车地点时
location, extracting the real
采取可运用于交互的 parameterValue 方法
values using the parameterValue
就可以提取出
method for the interaction.
真值
Finally we'll use those values,
我们最后将使用这些真值
again, configure our Unicorn
给最后这一批参数
Ride View for these last
再次配置 Unicorn 的乘车视图
parameters and tell Siri we're
并且告诉 Siri
handling them with our custom
我们要用自定义的尺寸对它们
size.
进行处理
This looks pretty good.
这看起来很不错
So let's build and run this one
那我们现在就来构建和运行
now.
一下看看
And now we've got our fully
现在我们就得到了非常具有
Unicorny custom ride view.
Unicorn 风格的自定义乘车视图
So that looks great.
看起来真棒
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Let's go back to the slides.
让我们再回到幻灯片
Just to recap, when configuring
我简单复述一下  当你在给参数
your view for parameters, know
配置视图时  要知道
that you'll be called multiple
你会被再三要求
times to configure your view.
对自己的视图进行配置
You're first going to be called
首先 你会被要求提供
with an empty set of parameters.
一个空白的参数集
So again, you can draw
那么还是这样 你可以提取
additional info, your own custom
附加信息  你自己定义
header.
标题
Or you can even handle
或许你甚至现在
parameters up front here.
就可以预先处理参数
You'll be called in order for a
你会被依次要求提供
set of parameters for a given
一组参数
interaction.
给某个特定的交互
You'll be able to find the set
你将在随后出现的
of parameters in the order in an
归档更新内容里
upcoming update to the
依次找到这一组
documentation.
参数
Finally, just go ahead and
最后 你只需继续
handle your parameters, return
处理你的参数 把尺寸
the size up to Siri and draw
返回给 Siri  再绘制
your view.
你的视图
In an upcoming seed we're going
下一步我们将
to add a parameter to the
添加一个参数
configureView method called
到 configureView 方法
Interactive Behavior.
这个参数叫 Interactive Behavior
So certain views and certain
所以某些视图
parameters have interactivity
和参数本身就关联着
associated with them.
交互性
So for example, the map, you can
我们以地图为例
tap it, you'll get another view.
你轻点它 就会出现另一种视图
That's like a next view.
就像是下一个视图
Certain views may launch your
某些视图可能会启动
app.
你的 App
So the Interactive Behavior
所以 Interactive Behavior 参数
parameter will give you hints
可以给你一些提示
about the type of interaction
提示这些参数
that's available for these
可以使用哪一种
parameters.
交互类型
And you can use that to
你还可以用它
customize your view as well.
来自定义你的视图
There will also be another
另外还有一种方法
method called Description of
叫做界面参数描述
Interface Parameters on your
它和你的
Intents UIExtension Context,
Intents UI extension 语境有关
which you can use during
你可以在
debugging in order to printout
调试过程中用它来
the order of parameters and the
打印输出某个特定交互中的
set of parameters during a give
参数顺序以及这个
interaction.
参数集
So, this is the brand new
看 这就是全新的
INInteraction API.
INInteraction API
It's super powerful.
它超级强大
And we can't wait to see what
我们迫不及待地想看到
you guys build with it.
大家准备用它构建出怎样的惊喜
I'm going to hand it back to
我要把讲台交还给 Sirisha
Sirisha to talk about some
让她来展示一些
additional enhancements.
新增的优化功能
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Tin.
&gt;&gt;谢谢你，Tin
Along with adding more domains
除了添加更多的应用域
and the powerful parameters Tin
和强大的参数
just introduced, we've spent a
就像刚才 Tin 介绍的那样
lot of time enhancing our
我们还投入了大量时间
systems and APIs.
来增强我们的系统和 API
I'm not going to go over all of
我不打算把这些成果全部展示一遍
them, but I want to talk about
但是我想谈谈
two of them.
其中的两样
First, I'll cover Background
首先 我要谈谈
Workout App Intent Handling, an
后台体能训练 App Intent 处理
ability to start workout apps in
这是一项新能力
background.
它可以在后台启动健身的 App
And Alternative App Names.
另一个就是 App 替换名称
We'll get to it in a minute.
我们很快就会讲到这项新功能
Workouts are very popular
健身广受欢迎的
intents.
Intent
Users love to use Siri to
用户们喜欢用 Siri 来
control their workouts.
掌握健身活动
It's very easy.
它操作非常简单
The current implementation when
当前的执行情况是
user requests any action on a
当用户向某个健身 App 发出
workout, Siri calls the
请求指令时 Siri 会调用
extension.
Extension
And then the extension hands it
接下来 Extension 又会把请求
over to the app.
传递给 App
And thus Siri asking permission
如果设备已经锁定
for the user if the device is
Siri 会在启动 App 之前
locked before launching the app.
请求用户许可
We changed this a bit this year.
今年 我们在这方面做了些改变
We wanted to make sure that
我们想要确保
before launching the app we
App 在前台启动之前
launched the app instead of in
后台就已经
the foreground, but in the
启动了 App 而不是等到
background.
在前台显示过后
So users can now just talk to
所以 用户现在只要对
Siri and have the app launched.
Siri 说话 App 就能成功启动
And this is for the Workout
这是为使用 iOS11 的
Intents starting iOS 11.
健身 Intent 所准备的
Let's look in the code.
现在我们来看看代码
This is the current
这是目前的
implementation.
执行情况
A sample code for a start
启动健身 Intent 的
workout intent response.
一个响应码样例
The extension usually returns
Extension 通常会返回
continuing app, which when Siri
继续 App 当 Siri
calls the application method in
调用 UI 应用授权里的
the UI application delegate,
应用方法时
passing the NS userActivity,
Extension 会让 NS userActivity 通过
prompting an app launch.
并提示启动 App
We've added two new things to
我们已经新增了两个代码
change the flow.
以改变当前的流程
We have added a new intent
我们添加了一个新的 Intent
response code Handle an App.
响应码 Handle an App
So, you have a choice to return
因此 你可以选择返回
Handle an App response code to
Handle an App 响应码
make sure that we call a new
来确认我们调用了
application method.
新的应用方法
We've added a new application
我们在 UI 应用授权上
method on the UI Application
新增了一个
Delegate.
应用方法
This takes IN Intent and a
这需要采用 IN Intent 和
completion handler.
Completion Handler
So, when you pass in Handle an
所以 当你以 Intent 反应码的形式
App as an intent response code,
传递 Handle an App
and implement the new
并执行新的
application method, we will call
应用方法时 我们将调用
the new application method,
新的应用方法
prompting to launch the app in
在后台提示
the background.
启动 App
This is very useful when the
当用户只想启动或暂停健身
users just want to start Workout
甚至是通过 AirPods 来操作时
or pause, even through airports.
它也非常有用
They don't even have to touch
他们甚至都不必触碰
the device.
设备
Let's take a quick look at the
我们来快速地看一下
flow.
这个流程
How does this look?
看起来如何？
User wants to start a workout.
用户想要开始一项体能训练
We launch the extension, call
我们启动 Extension  调用
the handle method.
处理方法
And the extension returns the
Extension 就会返回
new intent response code, Handle
新的 Intent 响应码  即 Handle
an App.
an App
And then Siri calls the
接着 Siri 以新的应用方法
application, the new application
调用这个应用程序
method, passing the IN Intent
传递 IN Intent
and the completion handler.
以及 Completion Handler
And that completion block
这个完成代码块
inserts the intent response
嵌入了 Intent 响应
code.
代码
And then application will be
于是 应用程序将在
launched in the background and
后台启动 并且
passing the success back to Siri
将成功操作的信息反馈给 Siri
with the completion of the
告知活动
activity.
已完成
We believe this will make user's
我们认为这将会让用户
experience more easy, more
在控制自己的体能训练计划时
seamless while controlling their
操作体验更加便捷
workouts.
流畅
And we're very excited for this.
对于这一点 我们感到很兴奋
The second enhancement I'm going
今天我要谈论的
to talk about today is
第二个优化功能是
alternative app names.
App 的别名
Usually user can actually call
通常情况下 用户确实会用
an app in different names,
各种各样的名字来
different varieties.
指代一个 App
Like UnicornPay can be just
比如 UnicornPay 会被
called as Unicorn.
简称为 Unicorn
UnicornPay or CornPay.
UnicornPay 或 CornPay
We want to make sure that we
我们想确保能够
understand all the variations of
理解用户使用的
the app names the user uses and
所有 App 名称变体
invoke the right app.
以便准确对应地启用 App
So, to make this happen, we've
因此 为了实现这一目标 我们
introduced a new field
将一个新字段
AlternativeAppName in the
AlternativeAppName
.plist.
引入 .plist
While registering in the .plist
当你注册 .plist 时
you have the ability to fill in
你可以填写
all the app names that you think
所有你认为
a user might use to refer to
用户可能用来称呼
your app.
这个 App 的名称
There is a field called
有一个字段叫做
AlternativeAppNames which takes
AlternativeAppNames 里面填写了
the actual names and then the
各个实际的名称 同时你也可以
pronunciation hint you can also
填写发音提示
fill in, if you think that's
如果你觉得有
necessary.
必要的话
This will help Siri understand
这将帮助 Siri 理解
all the variation of the app
所有 App 名称的变体
names and make sure to invoke
从而确保唤起
and call the right app the user
并调用这位用户
is expecting.
期待运行的 App
So far we've introduced new
到目前为止 我们已经介绍了新的
domains, Lists and Notes, and
域、列表、备忘录和
visual codes.
可视码
And new intents in our Payments
以及付款域里的
domain to support accounts.
新 Intent 用来支持账户管理
Brand new APIs to give you more
全新的 API 可以让你
control to customize the views.
在自定义设置视图时获得更多掌控
My colleague Tin introduced
我的同事 Tin 刚才已经介绍过
this.
这一点
And finally, the enhancements
最后 我们的一些优化功能
like starting a workout app in
例如  在后台开启健身 App
the background and also giving
以及让大家能够向我们
you the ability to provide us
提供你认为用户
all the alternative app names
有可能使用的
that you think a user can call.
所有 App 别名
Please visit our website
请大家访问我们的网站
developer.apple.com for more
developer.apple.com 以便
information under our session
获得这次 214 会议的
214.
更多信息
We have another session coming
接下来我们将进行另一场会议
up, Making Great SiriKit
“打造强大的 SiriKit 体验”
Experiences, where our experts
我们的专家将
will talk about methodologies,
向大家介绍  在编写
techniques, helpful hints you
Siri Extension 时
can use while you're writing in
可能用到的方法和技术
Siri Extension.
并提供各种有益提示
Thank you all for joining us
感谢大家参加
today.
今天的会议
We're very excited to see all
我们非常期待能看到
the new things you're going to
大家使用我们全新的 API
bring using our new APIs.
并带来各种全新事物
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]